=Who Stole My Kiss=
= من سرق قبلتي =
=Episode 9=
= الحلقة 9 =
Hello.
مرحبًا.
(Ting, you can come back to the company.)
(تينج ، يمكنك العودة إلى الشركة).
Come back to the company?
أعود إلى الشركة؟
Mr. Lu has got the evidence that
السيد لو لديه الدليل على ذلك
you were framed in the afternoon
كنت مؤطرا في فترة ما بعد الظهر
and given it to the police.
وأعطوها للشرطة.
Now, everything has come to light.
الآن ، ظهر كل شيء.
(Ting, you can come back to work here.)
(تينج ، يمكنك العودة للعمل هنا.)
Evidence?
شهادة؟
But, didn't our company decide
لكن ، ألم تقرر شركتنا
to collaborate with Qin Mochi
للتعاون مع تشين موتشي
and make him the ambassador?
وجعله السفير؟
That was the leader's plan.
كانت تلك خطة القائد.
But Mr. Lu
لكن السيد لو
has made Qin Mochi's manager
جعل تشين موتشي مديرًا
to tell the truth
لتخبر الحقيقة
(and he's got it recorded.)
(وقد سجلها).
(The valid evidence)
(الدليل الصحيح)
has proven that they were at fault.
لقد أثبتوا أنهم كانوا على خطأ.
(That's great.)
(هذا عظيم.)
(I've misunderstood master.)
(لقد أسأت فهم السيد.)
- Good morning, Ting. - Good morning.
- صباح الخير تينغ.  - صباح الخير.
Not bad, Tingting.
ليس سيئا ، تينجتينج.
Ting.
تينغ.
Mr. Lu's looking for you.
السيد "لو" يبحث عنك.
Master, good morning.
سيدي صباح الخير.
You've got to know the matter, right?
عليك أن تعرف الأمر ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Thank you for helping me.
شكرا لمساعدتي.
At the same time,
في نفس الوقت،
I'd like to apologise to you.
أود أن أعتذر لك.
I was being impulsive in the cafe the other day.
كنت مندفعًا في المقهى ذلك اليوم.
I was too immature.
كنت غير ناضج جدا.
I'll consider things from the company's perspective
سأفكر في الأمور من منظور الشركة
more often in the future.
في كثير من الأحيان في المستقبل.
Suspending you
يعلقك
and the endorsement agreement
واتفاقية المصادقة
were part of the plan.
كانت جزءًا من الخطة.
I didn't tell you in the beginning
لم أخبرك في البداية
because I wanted to tell you
لأنني أردت أن أخبرك
when everything is solved.
عندما يتم حل كل شيء.
No worries, master.
لا تقلق يا سيد.
I've figured it out.
لقد اكتشفت ذلك.
I won't be reckless anymore.
لن أكون متهورًا بعد الآن.
Okay, get back to work.
حسنًا ، عد إلى العمل.
Master, here are some gifts
سيدي ، إليك بعض الهدايا
as a token of appreciation.
كعربون تقدير.
Ting.
تينغ.
Congratulations for coming back strong.
ألف مبروك لعودة قوية.
This cactus is a gift for you.
هذا الصبار هدية لك.
If anyone bullies you again,
إذا كان أي شخص يتنمر عليك مرة أخرى ،
use the cactus to poke him.
استخدم الصبار لكزه.
I think you're trying to poke me.
أعتقد أنك تحاول أن تزعجني.
Anyways, thank you.
على أي حال ، شكرا لك.
But Ting,
لكن تينج ،
why are you wearing like this today?
لماذا ترتدي مثل هذا اليوم
I'm changing my fashion style. What's wrong?
أنا أغير أسلوبي في الموضة.  ما هو الخطأ؟
Is it not nice?
أليس من الجميل؟
You were cuter.
كنت لطيفا.
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
This is called growing up.
هذا يسمى النمو.
You were not around
لم تكن في الجوار
and I was so lonely as your assistant.
وكنت وحيدًا جدًا بصفتي مساعدك.
No one was taking care of me.
لم يكن أحد يهتم بي.
Thank you for stepping up
شكرا لك على التقدم
for me in the cafe the other day.
بالنسبة لي في المقهى ذلك اليوم.
I didn't know you acted like a man
لم أكن أعلم أنك تتصرف كرجل
at the critical moment.
في اللحظة الحرجة.
A man
رجل
doesn't need muscle and height,
لا تحتاج إلى عضلات وطول ،
but we must have the attitude.
ولكن يجب أن يكون لدينا الموقف.
Ting,
تينغ ،
how are you going to thank me?
كيف ستشكرني
(Yiya family restaurant)
(مطعم يا عائلي)
The portion in this restaurant
(مطعم Yiya العائلي) الجزء الموجود في هذا المطعم
is so small.
صغير جدا.
It's not enough?
إنه لا يكفى؟
It's okay. Order more.
حسنا.  أطلب المزيد.
No worries. I won't go broke.
لا داعى للقلق.  لن أفلس.
Excuse me, three more kids meals.
معذرة ، ثلاث وجبات أخرى للأطفال.
Eat more.
كل أكثر.
You need to grow your body.
أنت بحاجة إلى نمو جسمك.
Ting,
تينغ ،
why are you eating so little?
لماذا تأكل قليلا جدا
I'm getting old.
انا اتقدم بالسن.
Unlike you.
على خلافك.
Young people have a great appetite.
الشباب لديهم شهية كبيرة.
You're not old.
أنت لست كبير السن.
Your skin is good.
بشرتك جيدة.
If we're walking on the street,
إذا كنا نسير في الشارع ،
others might think you're my younger sister.
قد يعتقد الآخرون أنك أختي الصغرى.
I don't have a silly brother like you.
ليس لدي أخ سخيف مثلك.
Ting,
تينغ ،
you're not good at drinking.
أنت لا تجيد الشرب.
Please don't drink too much.
من فضلك لا تشرب كثيرا.
If you act like the other night again,
إذا كنت تتصرف مثل تلك الليلة مرة أخرى ،
I can't stop you.
لا استطيع منعك.
That night?
تلك الليلة؟
What did I do?
ماذا فعلت؟
You were active and dominating that night.
كنت نشيطًا ومسيطرًا في تلك الليلة.
You were acting willfully.
كنت تتصرف عمدا.
You even made me blush.
حتى أنك جعلتني أخجل.
Blush?
احمر خدود؟
Yes, Ting.
نعم ، تينغ.
When are you going to do
متى ستفعل
what you promised me?
ماذا وعدتني
(Goodness me. Did he)
(الخير لي. هل هو)
(kiss me?)
(قبّلني؟)
(You'll be my people from now on.)
(ستصبح شعبي من الآن فصاعدًا.)
(I'll be responsible for you.)
(سأكون مسؤولاً عنك.)
This is the last conversation
هذه هي المحادثة الأخيرة
we had that night.
قضينا تلك الليلة.
I'm done.
أنا انتهيت.
Not bad, Han Tingting.
ليس سيئا ، هان تينجتينج.
Congratulations
تهانينا
for having a 19-year-old cute boy
لوجود صبي لطيف يبلغ من العمر 19 عامًا
and starting a sweet relationship.
وبدء علاقة حلوة.
No way.
مستحيل.
He's just a kid.
إنه مجرد طفل.
He knows nothing at all.
إنه لا يعرف شيئًا على الإطلاق.
I usually take care of him like my son
أنا عادة أعتني به مثل ابني
in the office.
في المكتب.
Do you think I can date my son?
هل تعتقد أنه يمكنني مواعدة ابني؟
Don't refuse it first.
لا ترفضها أولاً.
Look at his Moment.
انظر إلى لحظته.
Besides working out and nice food,
إلى جانب التمارين والطعام اللطيف ،
look at this photo
انظر الى هذه الصورة
and this photo,
وهذه الصورة ،
it's all the selfie that he took with you.
إنها كل الصور الشخصية التي أخذها معك.
Look at the company group photo.
انظر إلى الصورة الجماعية للشركة.
Who is that standing next to you?
من يقف بجانبك؟
It's Lu Yuanyu.
إنه لو Yuanyu.
Look at how he looks
انظر كيف يبدو
at you. So sweet.
عليك.  حلو جدا.
He's so cute.
انه لطيف جدا.
Won't you consider him?
ألا تعتبره؟
I can't take it.
لا أستطيع أخذها.
I'll get sick.
سأمرض.
Are you sure he's not your type?
هل أنت متأكد من أنه ليس من نوعك؟
What if he suits you
ماذا لو كان يناسبك
and won't cause you sick?
ولن يسبب لك المرض؟
But if I'm going out with him,
لكن إذا خرجت معه ،
I'll be his girlfriend, superior,
سأكون صديقته ، أيها الرئيس ،
elder sister, mother and maid.
الأخت الكبرى ، الأم والخادمة.
That's five roles.
هذه خمسة أدوار.
I'm not Naruto.
أنا لست ناروتو.
He's not Hinata Hyuga either.
إنه ليس هيناتا هيوجا أيضًا.
It's not worth it for me.
لا يستحق كل هذا العناء بالنسبة لي.
What if the one who kissed you
ماذا لو من قبلك
was Lu Yuanyu? What will you do?
هل كان لو Yuanyu؟  ماذا ستفعل؟
If the one who kissed you was Lu Yuanyu,
إذا كان الشخص الذي قبلك هو لو Yuanyu ،
I will
أنا سوف
pretend like I've forgotten it.
تظاهر وكأنني نسيتها.
As long as I don't admit it,
طالما أنني لا أعترف بذلك ،
it's like it has never happened.
يبدو الأمر كما لو أنه لم يحدث أبدًا.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'm having my period pain.
أعاني من آلام الدورة الشهرية.
Now that I think of the one
الآن بعد أن أفكر في الواحد
who kissed me might be Lu Yuanyu,
من قبلني قد يكون لو Yuanyu ،
I'm...
انا...
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
Let's go to bed.
دعنا نذهب إلى السرير.
Let me get you some hot water.
دعني أحضر لك بعض الماء الساخن.
Please don't be Lu Yuanyu.
من فضلك لا تكون لو Yuanyu.
(I'm running late!)
(أنا متأخر!)
(Haiyuting)
(هاييوتينج)
♪Does he like you?♪
♪ هل يحبك؟ ♪
♪Don't rush to interrupt♪
♪ لا تتسرع في المقاطعة ♪
♪You're being silent♪
♪ أنت صامت ♪
♪I lost the courage to talk♪
♪ فقدت الشجاعة للحديث ♪
♪That day was a suitable timing♪
كان ذلك اليوم هو التوقيت المناسب
♪I wanted to tell you♪
♪ أردت أن أخبرك ♪
♪Because you're gentle♪
♪ لأنك لطيف ♪
♪Like printed in my heart♪
♪ مثل المطبوع في قلبي ♪
♪Wanted to♪
♪ مطلوب
♪Embrace your breath♪
♪ احتضان أنفاسك ♪
♪Only you can♪
♪ أنت فقط تستطيع ♪
♪Solve the cute riddle♪
♪ حل اللغز اللطيف ♪
♪I like your♪
♪ أنا معجب بك ♪
♪Silly face♪
♪ وجه سخيف ♪
♪So happiness is always mentioned♪
♪ فدائما ما تذكر السعادة
♪It's in the bottom of my heart♪
♪ إنها في أعماق قلبي ♪
♪There are wind, rain and you♪
هناك رياح ومطر وأنت ♪
♪Every day♪
♪ كل يوم ♪
♪You've slowly become♪
♪ لقد أصبحت ببطء ♪
♪The best weather in my eyes♪
♪ أحلى طقس في عيني ♪
♪Holding me in your arms♪
أمسكني بين ذراعيك ♪
♪I like♪
♪ أحب ♪
♪Being with you♪
التواجد معك ♪